khmerfun.net 2012-04-09

# Privacy Policy » Khmer Social Networking Community

**PLEASE READ THIS PRIVACY STATEMENT CAREFULLY**

The only personal information we collect is the personal information you choose to give us. The purpose of this Privacy Statement is to tell you what information we gather on this website and how we use that information. 

This Privacy Statement applies only to the KhmerFun website, with a homepage located at www.KhmerFun.com (the “Website”). This Privacy Statement does not apply to any other websites, and KhmerFun makes no representations as to the privacy practices of other websites.   
We may change this Privacy Statement at any time and for any reason. We encourage you to look to this Privacy Statement each time you visit the Website. By using this Website, you agree to the terms of this Privacy Statement. Please read our Terms of Use to understand the general rules about your use of this Website. 

**PROTECTING YOUR PRIVACY**   
The ways we protect and use information collected over this Website depends upon the type of information involved. Certain personal information, such as your full name, is used only for limited purposes. Other information, such as your login name, your posted messages, and responses to those messages, is not deemed confidential, may be shared freely with third parties, and will be posted on the Website. 

**WHAT IS NON-PERSONAL INFORMATION?**   
Each time a computer visits this Website we may collect certain information from that computer. This information is automatically collected from the computer’s web browser and may include information such as the following (“non-personal information”): - the type of web browser software the computer uses (for example, Chrome, Firefox or Internet Explorer) - the name of the domain from which the computer accessed the Internet - the Internet address of the website from which the computer linked directly to the Website - the date and time the computer accessed the Website   
**  
Non-personal information does not tell us who you are.**   
Also, we may place a text file called a cookie in the browser files of computers that visit this Website. Cookies are pieces of information issued by a website that, among other things, allow your computer to utilize all the features on this Website. If and when your computer accepts a cookie, the cookie may be stored on the computer’s hard drive. The information that we collect using cookies is non-personal information. US Government Information Bulletin (I-034) contains a good description of cookie technology at: http://www.ciac.org/ciac/bulletins/i-034.shtml. You are always free to decline our cookies if your browser permits, but some parts of the Website may not work properly for you if you do so. 

**WHAT DO WE DO WITH NON-PERSONAL INFORMATION?**   
We will use non-personal information to help us make the Website more useful to visitors and for other business purposes. For example, we may tell business partners how many computers visited this Website or what pages were most popular. We may prepare reports and other materials using non-personal information. Since these reports and materials contain no personal information, we may share them with others. 

**WHAT IS PERSONAL INFORMATION?**   
In the process of registering for a username and password, and in some other places on this Website, some visitors may have the chance to send us “personal information”. Personal information includes information that tells us specifically who a person is, such as a person’s name, email address, or similar identifying information.   
**  
HOW DO WE COLLECT PERSONAL INFORMATION?**   
The only way we learn or collect personal information online is if a visitor chooses to provide us with that information. For example, if you fill out a form to register as an KhmerFun member, you will tell us and we will learn your full name and email address.   
**  
HOW DO WE USE PERSONAL INFORMATION?**   
If you submit personal information, you agree that we may keep a record of the personal information. For example, we may keep a record of your name and e-mail address in order to keep track of the username and password we assigned to you. We also may use personal information to help us in our business, including but not limited to improving this Website and marketing and product development, or to contact you in the event you earn a cash award, gift certificate, or other award. You also agree that we may share personal information with other businesses that help us with these activities. For example, if you pay for a tour guide or tour package by Visa or MasterCard, we will share your name and card number with Visa or MasterCard so that we can process your payment. These other companies may not use or share your personal information with others except for the purpose of assisting us with our business activities pursuant to our request. Also, we may share personal information with other companies we do business with, such as business partners, affiliates, or successors. We may also share personal information if required to comply with a law, regulation, court order, or other legal process. We may share personal information to protect our rights or property.   
**  
POSTED INFORMATION.**   
Some information we collect will be posted on the Website, shared with third parties, and will not be treated as confidential. This information includes: (a) your chosen login name; (b) your Country and State if you choose to provide this information; (c) any message your choose to post as well as the replies of others to your message; and (d) the date and time of your previous visits to the Website. We may also display on the Website information related to your postings including but not limited to number of postings, number of responses, and various rankings of your postings by other members and the KhmerFun staff.   
**  
WHAT HAPPENS IF THE PRIVACY STATEMENT CHANGES?**   
If we decide to make a significant change to our Privacy Statement, we will post a notice on the homepage of the Website for a period of time after the change is made.   
**  
WHAT ABOUT PRIVACY ON OTHER SITES?**   
This Website may contain links to other websites. We provide these links for your convenience, but we do not review, control, or monitor the privacy practices of websites operated by others. We are not responsible for the performance of these sites or for your business dealings with them. Your use of other websites is subject to the terms and conditions of those websites, including the privacy policies of those websites. 

**ARE THERE SPECIAL RULES ABOUT CHILDREN’S PRIVACY?**   
This Website is designed for an adult audience only, and children should not use this Website. We will not intentionally collect online any personal information (such as a child’s name or e-mail address) from children under the age of 13. If you think that we have collected personal information from a child under the age of 13, please email us at support@KhmerFun.com. 

**HOW TO CONTACT US?**   
If you have questions or comments about this Privacy Statement, please send an email to support@KhmerFun.com.
